<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Movie AnyTime!</string>

    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="SeatSelected">Seat!!!</string>

    <string name="about_me1">The Avengers and their allies must be willing to sacrifice all in an attempt to defeat the powerful Thanos before his blitz of devastation and ruin puts an end to the universe.</string>
    <string name="details_content1">As the Avengers and their allies have continued to protect the world from threats too large for any one hero to handle, a new danger has emerged from the cosmic shadows: Thanos. A despot of intergalactic infamy, his goal is to collect all six Infinity Stones, artifacts of unimaginable power, and use them to inflict his twisted will on all of reality. Everything the Avengers have fought for has led up to this moment - the fate of Earth and existence itself has never been more uncertain. Written by Marvel Studios
    </string>
    <string name="about_me2">The life of a foster family in South Central Los Angeles, a few weeks before the city erupts in violence following the verdict of the Rodney King trial.</string>
    <string name="details_content2">
    An unfortunate letdown. It pains me to say this because this had the potential to be very good. "Kings" is a story centered around the LA riots which occurred in the early 90\'s. It\'s told through the perspective of a family who find themselves in the middle of the intense event.
        There was set-up for great drama, but the end result is an uneven mess with little to no pay-off. This movie had
        the most abrupt and out of nowhere endings that I\'ve seen all year. Early on we seem to be promised an emotional and
        riveting finale. And we never get that finale. It just sort of ends before the third act is taking shape. The first
        half of the film suffers a lot. I didn\'t form much of an attachment with the characters. The editing switches too quickly
        between people with little moments to breath and for you to get to know them. Besides, almost every scene during the
        first half consists of people yelling and talking over each other constantly. The pace is unfocused. You can only take
        so much loud shouting before your only wish is for people to calm down and be quiet for just a second. The silent or
        calmer scenes are precious because there are so few of them. Halle Berry gives a good performance and so does Daniel
        Craig. They are both like-able as their bonding slowly progresses throughout the story. If they only picked a better
        project to be apart of though. It was a waste of their talents. Lamar Johnson who plays Berry\'s son gets a lot screen-time, and he was really good playing a grounded and sympathetic character.
        There's much heavy lifting for him to do as he wants to make sense out of the situation and find some peaceful solution to many problems. I was on-board with his story-line until he, of course, disappears towards the end. The development of the character pretty much stopped just as it was about to get the most interesting. Tonally it's all pretty realistic with documentary like montage sequences. Well, except for one abstract dream scene involving Berry and Craig that confused half the audience. It was supposed to be "romantic", but it's like nothing else in the entire movie. The scene comes off as more comedic than anything because of how cheesy the presentation is. It was kind of embarrassing as well, which made me feel bad for the actors.The actual riot scenes weren't bad. It's the journey up to that point that's difficult to tolerate. If only they didn't let every dialogue scene be people yelling, shouting or screaming. The pulse can't be that high all the time. There needs to be some breathing. I like the actors and the director is respected, but they can't save the movie. We get some sprinkled decent moments, but there's just not enough of them. Oh, I'll give it a point for being shot on film. No complaints on cinematography. Don't rush out to see this one once it comes out. Catch it on VOD or something and be sure to not have the volume too high. Trust me, it's gonna get loud. My other summary of the film is: I like you guys, but better luck next time.

    </string>
    <string name="about_me3">Isabelle, Parisian artist, divorced mother, is looking for love, true love at last.</string>
    <string name="details_content3">Claire Denis\' "Let the Sun Shine In" is an exhausting and overwhelming experience, as is the choreography of romance and life it is set in. In the world of tinder, it\'s all 1s and 0s, but real life these days is much less binary and less immediately satisfying. You won\'t find that kind of easy romcom satisfaction in Denis\' film. One is buffeted by indecision, imprecision, and inaction while swimming in self doubt and self loathing. Isabelle, our stand-in for the duration, is emotionally exhausting. She asks a lot of her lovers and of the audience. She says "stay with me, stay," and Denis uses Juliette Binoche to maximum seductive affect but it\'s not an easy journey. Isabelle is, by turns, a strong woman with a lot to offer and who knows what she wants, but also a weak human being filled with doubt. She's a paradox and a contradiction, but she also understands without acknowledging that she will always have opportunities...another opportunity. She is someone who is exploring the boundaries of her self. It's perplexing territory to the men she meets but also to herself. Denis shows us as many facets of Isabelle as we are willing to see, that we can see. I think there's a lot more there than I could see at one sitting. A unique portrait. Her best film since "White Material." I'd love to talk to her about it!</string>
    <string name="about_me4">When the creator of a virtual reality world called the OASIS dies, he releases a video in which he challenges all OASIS users to find his Easter Egg, which will give the finder his fortune.</string>
    <string name="details_content4">If you haven\'t read the book, then this will be a nice fun film to watch with retro references, adventure, and a look at a world where everyone lives on VR.

If you have read the book then prepare to be left bemused, gutted, devastated and downright disappointed at what a mess that Spielberg has made from an amazing geek fest book into a mundane movie for the masses.

This movie could have been an absolute cult classic of a dystopian future with some amazing insights as to what a future society of Virtual Reality users would look like. But this movie has not only decided to skim over the details of the technology and how far integrated it is in every day life, not only forget building the characters story line and gradually introducing them, but instead has taken the basic story line, along with the characters and then a few key points, throw them in the air and where ever they land write a completely different story in between and Hollywood the hell out of it with absolutely no loyalty to the book. I can not even begin to list how much is missing that would make this film make more sense.

In fact this movie should NOT even have the honour of the title Ready Player One, instead it should be called GAME OVER, it is an insult to the book in every way possible.

If you are thinking of watching this movie and not read the book, then do as it is probably not a bad film but make sure you read the book after the movie and not before. If you have already read the book, and loved the book then I would not recommend going to see this as it will just infuriate and give you high blood pressure. Instead wait for the dvd so you can rant, shout and tut loudly at the screen without disturbing others.</string>
</resources>
